

# **BRUNO PAIVA TRIBST**

MOTION DESIGNER

July 30, 1984 | brazilian, married, 2 children

### **STATEMENT**

Motion Designer, a self-taught student of Traditional Animation, Illustration, 3D and Video editing and UI/UX. More than 15 years experienced professional, working as a Motiongrapher, Web Designer and Graphic Designer for TV Broadcasting in Brazil, Lebanon, Cyprus, Germany, Thailand and Canada.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

2021 - 2023

### AMAZING DISCOVERIES MINISTRY | CANADA

**Motion Designer** 

Video editing, Openers, 3D and 2D animation

2019 - 2021

### HOPE CHANNEL SOUTHEAST ASIA | THAILAND

**Post-Production Coordinator** 

Video editing, Openers, animation and Project managing

2016 - 2019

### **HOPE CHANNEL EUROPE | GERMANY**

**Motion and Graphic Designer** 

Animation Series, Openers and Printing Materials

2011 - 2013

### HOPE CHANNEL MIDDLE EAST | LEBANON Motion and Graphic Designer

Motion Graphics, Animation, SET Design and Printing

Materials for Arabic, Farsi and Turkish Programs.

2010 - 2011

## HOPE CHANNEL SOUTH AMERICA | BRAZIL Motiongrapher

Motion Graphics, Openers, Animation, 3D, StationID and Motion Advertising for Novo Tempo Records.

2009 - 2010

## HOPE CHANNEL SOUTH AMERICA | BRAZIL Art Director

Art Direction for TV Broadcasting (Portuguese and Spanish) and Graphics Projects Management.

2007 - 2009

### HOPE CHANNEL SOUTH AMERICA | BRAZIL Web Designer

Web design for Novo Tempo's websites Graphic Design and assistant in Motion Graphics

### CONTACT

Av. José Dini, 400

Taboão da Serra, SP - Brazil

**Tel**: +55 (11) 91788 9128

E-mail: bruno.tribst@gmail.com

LinkedIn: www.linkedin.com/in/brunotribst

Portfolio: www.noahstudio.space

#### **EDUCATION**

2013 - 2015 BACHELOR OF VISUAL ARTS, BA
Eastern Mediterranean University

Famagusta, Cyprus

2003 - 2005 ASC MULTIMEDIA DESIGN

Senac University Comm. & Arts

São Paulo, Brazil

### SKILLS

After Effects
Photoshop
Premiere
Animate
Illustrator
Nuke
Autodesk Maya
Blender
Fusion Studio
inDesign

English German

### **VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE**

#### Painter at BeyondWalls Art Project

A public art initiative called "Murals for Peace" launched in the Middle East in 2012 – Jordan | Tunisia | Egypt

### Art Assistant at NGO Vida Nova

Art Assistant for needy children in the favela (São Paulo, Brazil), creative activities and art class.